Guide to the League of Women Voters of New York State Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
League of Women Voters of New York State Records,
1912-1981.
League of Women Voters of New York State.
40 linear ft (ca. 31,100 items in 68 boxes, 26 volumes, & 7 oversize items).
Columbia University Rare Book and Manuscript Library, Butler Library,New York, NY 10027.
4079554
History
The League was originally formed as an auxiliary to the National American Woman Suffrage Association.
Scope and Content
Correspondence, minutes, reports, documents, scrapbooks, publications, memorabilia, and photographs. The general files, minutes, and reports reflect the varied activities and interests of the League, including apportionment, court reform, education, and voting rights. The historical files contain photographs, printed materials, and memorabilia, filed chronologically. Also included are the periodicals and publications of the League, scrapbooks arranged chronologically, and "Mailbooks", or volumes of mimeographed reports and announcements which were sent to branches and board members. Among the major correspondentrs are: Thomas E. Dewey, Herbert H. Hehman, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Franklin D. Roosevelt, and Alfred Smith.
1986 ADDITION: Subject files and printed materials, 1961-1978.
1988 ADDITION: Subject files, 1972-1981.
Arrangement
Selected materials cataloged; remainder arranged.
Subjects
Democratic Party (U.S.); League of Women Voters (U.S.); National American Woman Suffrage Association.; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); Dewey, Thomas E. (Thomas Edmund), 1902-1971.; Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979.; Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Franklin Delano), 1882-1945.; Smith, Alfred Emanuel, 1873-1944.; United States--Foreign relations.; United States--Officials and employees.; New York (State)--Politics and government--1865-1950.; New York (State)--Politics and government--1951-; Apportionment.; City planning.; Courts--New York (State); Ecology--New York (State); Education--New York (State); Educational change--New York (State); Elections--New York (State); Elections--Corrupt practices--New York (State); Environmental protection.; Equal rights amendments.; Legislative bodies--Reform.; Lobbying.; Municipal government--New York (State); Political participation--New York (State); Politics, Practical--New York (State); Schools--New York (State); Sex discrimination--New York (State); Social problems.; Suffrage.; State governments.; Voter registration--New York (State)--New York.; Voter registration--New York (State); Voting--New York (State); Women.; Women in politics--New York (State); Women--New York (State)--Societies and clubs.; Announcements.; Annual reports.; Biographies.; Bylaws.; Certificates.; Handbooks.; Interviews.; Minutes.; Photographs.; Plaques.; Poems.; Press releases.; Reports.; Scrapbooks.; Songs.; Testimony.
Acquisition
1981 M-1981 The League Gift
Gift of the League of Women Voters of New York State, 1981, 1986 & 1988.
Related Material
All records post-1981 are housed at the New York State Library, Albany.
- Series I: Catalogued Correspondence
  - Byrne, James (Box 1)
  - Dewey, Thomas E. (Box 1)
  - Fish, Hamilton (Box 1)
  - Hull, Cordell (Box 1)
  - Lefkowitz, Louis J. (Box 1)
  - Lehman, Herbert H. (Box 1)
  - Lindsay, Samuel McCune (Box 1)
  - MacCroacken, Henry N. (Box 1)
  - Meyer, Annie Nathan (Box 1)
  - Miller, Nathan L. (Box 1)
  - Perkins, Frances (Box 1)
  - Rockefeller, John D. Jr. (Box 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 1)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin Delano (Box 1)
  - Smith, Alfred E. (Box 1)
  - Strauss, Anna Lord (Box 1)
  - Thompson, Dorothy (Box 1)
  - Wallace, Schuyler C. (Box 1)
  - Wilson, Malcolm (Box 1)
- Series II: Catalogued Manuscripts and Documents
  - Catt, Carrie Chapman (Box 1)
  - Dewey, Thomas E. (Box 1)
  - Harriman, W. Averell (Box 1)
  - Lehman, Herbert H. (Box 1)
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Box 1)
- Series III: General Files
  - Correspondence, General, 1973-1975 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, National, 1971-1975 (Box 2)
  - Apportionment, 1943-1964 (Box 2)
  - By-Laws, 1912-1957 (Box 2)
- Series IV: Annual Reports
  - Annual Reports, 1959-1970 (Box 3)
- Series V: Constitution
  - Constitution, New York State (Box 4)
  - Constitution Making, (2 Folders) (Box 4)
  - Constitutional Convention, 1957-1977 (Box 4)
- Series VI: Conventions
  - Conventions, 1951-1963 (Box 5)
  - Conventions (Box 6)
  - Conventions, 1965-1969 (Box 6)
- Series VII: Councils
  - Councils, 1960-1970 (Box 7)
- Series VIII: Court Reforms
  - Court Reforms, 1955-1964 (Box 8)
- Series IX: Education and Elections
  - Education, 1959-1969 (Box 9)
  - Elections, 1951-1964 (Box 9)
  - Erie Barge Canal Study Group, 1971-1972 (Box 10)
  - Hudson Mohawk Vasin District 1968 (Box 10)
  - Sears Roebuck Leadership Conferences, 1964 (Box 10)
  - State Program, 1920-1948 (Box 10)
  - State Program, 1939-1972 (Box 11)
  - Statements, Hearings and Press Releases (Box 11)
  - Susquehanna Basin, 1966-1975 (Box 11)
  - Voters Service, 1937-1970 (Box 12)
- Series X: Historical Files
  - Historical Files (including photographs), 1912-1916 (primarily women's suffrage clippings) (Box 13)
  - 1925-1949 (Box 14)
  - 1950-1967 (Box 15)
  - 1967-1972 (Box 16)
  - Biographies A-Z (Box 17)
  - Biographies Seneca1 Falls Historical Society (Box 17)
- Series XI: Minutes and Reports
  - Legislative and Program Committees, 1923-19 29; 1936-1943 (Box 18)
  - Legislative and Program Committees, 1944-1950, 1954-1958 (Box 19)
  - State Board, 1960-1962 (Box 20)
  - State Board, 1963-1965 (Box 21)
- Series XII: Periodicals
  - League of Women Voters 3 of NYS (Box 22)
  - Weekly News, 1921-1933 (Box 22)
  - Weekly News, 1934-1936 (Box 23)
  - Monthly News, 1936-1954 (Box 23)
  - New York State Voter, 1955-1977 (Box 23)
  - Facts for Voters, 1943-1970 (Box 24)
  - Legislative Forecast and Reviews, 1949-1965 (Box 24)
  - Legislative News Service, 1962-1969, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
- Series XIII: Publications
  - Kits, Reports and Pamphlets (Box 25)
- Series XIV: Mailbooks
  - Mimeograph reports and announcements to branches, board members, etc. (Box 25)
  - March - August 1962 (Box 26)
  - September 1962 - April 1964 (Box 27)
  - May - December 1964 (Box 28)
  - December 1966 - March 1967 (Box 28)
  - April 1967 - January 1968 (Box 29)
  - February 1968 - March 1969 (Box 30)
  - April 1969 - June 1970 (Box 31)
  - July 1970 - October 1971 (Box 32)
  - November 1971 - December 1972 (Box 33)
  - 1973 (Box 34)
  - 1974 (Box 35)
  - 1975 (Box 36)
- Series XV: Scrapbooks
  - 1. 1923-1925 (Box 105)
  - 2. 1927-1928 (Box 105)
  - 3. 1928-1929 (Box 105)
  - 4. 1929-1930 (Box 105)
  - 5. 1930-1931 (Box 105)
  - 6. 1931-1932 (Box 106)
  - 7. 1930-1935 (Box 106)
  - 8. 1932-1933 (Box 106)
  - 9. 1933-1934 (Box 106)
  - 10. 1934-1935 (Box 106)
  - 11. 1935 (February-December) (Box 107)
  - 12. December 1935 (Box 107)
  - 13. 1936-1937 (Box 107)
  - 14. 1937-1938 (Box 107)
  - 15. 1938 (March-September) (Box 107)
  - 16. 1938-1939 (Box 108)
  - 17. 1939-1940 (Box 108)
  - 18. 1940-1941 (Box 108)
  - 19. 1941- (Box 108)
  - 20. Miscellaneous [Onsite]
  - 21. Miscellaneous [Onsite]
  - 22. Miscellaneous [Onsite]
  - 23 Miscellaneous (Box 108)
  - 24 Miscellaneous [Onsite]
  - 25 Miscellaneous [Onsite]
  - 26 Miscellaneous [Onsite]
- Series XVI: Plaques and Certificates
  - Scrapbook: "News of the League Aroung the State" 1947-1948 (Box 560)
  - Proclamation: Averell W. Harriman, Albany August 28, 1958 (Box 560)
  - Proclamation: "Roof-raising Day" John V. Lindsay, New York, August 29, 1970 (Box 560)
  - Proclamation: Nelson A. Rockefeller, Albany April, 13, 1969 (Box 560)
  - Clippings, 1960-1964 (Box 561)
  - "News of the League Around the State" 1951-1953 (Box 561)
  - Scrapbook of Internal Documents, 1948-1949 (Box 562)
  - Proclamation: Nelson A. Rockefeller, Albany May 11, 1973 (Box 562)
  - The League Story (Box 563)
  - Scrapbook of Clippings, 1924-1928 (Box 563)
  - Political Cartoon. Presented by LWV-Hampstead Central, May 15, 1973 (Box 564)
  - Plaque: Proclamation proposing a Woman's Suffrage Amendment (Box 564)
  - Citation of Honor for Mabel Russell (Box 564)
- Series XVII:Subject Files
  - Annual Reports, 1968-1975, (5 Folders) (Box 37)
  - Apportionment, 1965-1975, (4 Folders) (Box 37)
  - Candidates-Meetings, Questions (Box 37)
  - Community Development Article and Campaign, 1971 (Box 37)
  - Consensus Reports-English Literacy (Box 37)
  - Consensus Summaries-Education, 1972-1973 (Box 37)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 37)
  - DC Ratification, 1970-1975 (Box 37)
  - Education Finance, 1972-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 38)
  - ERA New York State, 1975, (2 Folders) (Box 38)
  - Financing the League, 1975 (Box 38)
  - General State Program, 1968-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 38)
  - Housing New York State, 1970-1975 (Box 39)
  - Human Resources, 1967-1976 (4 Folders) (Box 39)
  - Human Resources-Education, 1970-1975 (Box 39)
  - Human Resources-ERA Federal, 1972-1975 (Box 39)
  - Human Resources-Indians, 1973 (Box 39)
  - Human Resources-Welfare, 1970-1975 (Box 39)
  - Inter-League Council of the Delaware River Basin, 1970-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 40)
  - Inter-League Groups-Tri-State, 1972-1975 (Box 40)
  - International Relations, 1972-1975 (Box 40)
  - International Relations-China, 1971-1974 (Box 40)
  - International Relations-Trade, 1970-1975 (Box 41)
  - International Relations-UN, 1969-1975 (Box 41)
  - Interview with Legislators, 1972-1975 (Box 41)
  - League of Women Voters of WYS (Box 41)
  - Judicial, 1965-1971, (4 Folders) (Box 41)
  - Judical, 1971-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 42)
  - Judical-Canons of Ethics (Box 42)
  - Legislative Action General, 1970-1975 (Box 42)
  - Local League Correspondence, 1975 (Box 42)
  - Local Program, 1975 (Box 42)
  - Metropolitan Area Problems, 1960 (Box 42)
  - Money Budget-LWV New York State, 1971-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 42)
  - Money Development-LWV New York State, 1971-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 43)
  - Money Finance-LWV New York State, 1964, 1968, 1971-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 43)
  - Money Foundation for Citizen Education, 1971-1975 (Box 43)
  - Money Projects, 1972-1975 (Box 43)
  - National Overseas Education Fund, 1970-1975 (Box 43)
  - Natural Resources-Air, 1971-1975 (Box 43)
  - Natural Resources-Costal Zone Management Shelved (Box 44)
  - Natural Resources-Energy, 1974-1975 (Box 44)
  - Natural Resources-Environmental Quality, 1971-1976, (3 Folders) (Box 44)
  - Natural Resources-Land Use, 1973-1975, (2 Folders) (Box 44)
  - Natural Resources-Solid Waste, 1971-1974 (Box 45)
  - Natural Resources-Transportation, 1972-1978 (Box 45)
  - Natural Resources-Water, 1967, 1971-1974 (Box 45)
  - Organization Committee Minutes, 1949-1953 (Box 45)
  - President's Letters, 1975 (Box 45)
  - Selection of Judges, 1946-1950 (Box 45)
  - State Board Minutes and Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 45)
  - State Board Minutes and Reports, 1968-1975 (Box 46)
  - State Board Minutes and Reports, 1975-October 1976 (Box 47)
  - State Board Minutes and Reports, November 1976-March 1977 June-July 1977 September, 1977 (Box 48)
  - State Board Minutes and Reports, November 1977-December 1978 (Box 49)
  - State By-Laws Revision Committee (Box 50)
  - State Convention LWV, 1961, 1963, 1965, 1969, 1971 & 1973 ^ved oil-site (Box 50)
  - State Convention Workbook, 1963, 1965 & 1967 (Box 50)
  - State Council Minutes, 1962, 1964, (4 Folders) (Box 50)
  - State Council Minutes, 1966, 1968, 1970, 1972 & 1974 (Box 51)
  - State Finances, 1971-1972, 1974-1975 (Box 51)
  - State Program-Action Ballot Issues (Box 51)
  - State Voter, January-Dec ember 1966-1971, 1974-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 51)
  - Urban Crisis-Revenue Sharing (Box 52)
  - Voters Facts, 1972-1975 (Box 52)
  - Voters Service-General, 1971-1975, (3 Folders) (Box 52)
  - Voting Machine, 1961-1975 (Box 52)
  - Welfare Education, 1975 (Box 52)
  - Women's Issues, 1974-1975 (Box 52)
- Series XVIII:Printed Materials
  - Amendments Flyer, 1975 (Box 53)
  - Apportionment Flyer (Box 53)
  - Apportionment Resource Kit (Box 53)
  - Beverage Container Legislation (Box 53)
  - Community Development Campaign (Box 53)
  - Community Development Flyer (Box 53)
  - Constitutional Flyer, 1967 (Box 53)
  - Designations Petitions (Box 53)
  - Discussion Kits (Box 53)
  - Education Resource Kit (Box 53)
  - ERA Campaign Kit (Box 53)
  - ERA Fables and Facts (Box 53)
  - Environmental Quality-Wetlands and Hood Plain Management (Box 53)
  - Fact Sheet-Boces Study Kit (Box 53)
  - Financing Education Flyer (Box 53)
  - "Hey, Look Us Over", 1973-1974 (Box 53)
  - Home Rule-District of Columbia (Box 53)
  - Housing Flyers (Box 53)
  - Institutes Spring and Fall Training, 1971-1975 (Box 53)
  - It Made a Difference (Box 53)
  - League of Women Voters-Flyers-Membership (Box 53)
  - League of Women Voters in Action, 1962, 1975 (Box 53)
  - Legislative News Service, 1964 (Box 53)
  - Litigation Institute, 1973 (Box 53)
  - Local League Handbook (Box 53)
  - Local Program Handbook (Box 53)
  - Membership, 1966-1975 (Box 53)
  - Monthly News (Box 54)
  - New York State-A Citizen Handbook (Box 54)
  - New York State Legislative, 1975 (Box 54)
  - Pretrail Procedures in the Criminal Courts, 1974-1975 (Box 54)
  - Program Review (Box 54)
  - Publications-General, 1971-1975 (Box 54)
  - Publications-Promotion, 1971-1976 (Box 54)
  - Question and Answer about Merit-Selection of Judges (Box 55)
  - Recommendations Policy-General (Box 55)
  - Sewage Flyers (Box 55)
  - Songs and poems (Box 55)
  - State Board Handbook (Box 55)
  - Surban League Conference, 1970 (Box 55)
  - Voter Service (Box 55)
  - Unarranged Books and Pamphlets (Box 55)
  - Unarranged Books (Box 56)
- Series XIX: 1988 Addition, 1972 - 1981
  - Action File, 1977 (Box 57)
  - Action File, 1978 (Box 57)
  - Action-Lobbying, 1974-1976 (Box 57)
  - Action-Techniques, 1973-1976 (Box 57)
  - Albany Office-Budget, supply prices, etc., 1975-1976 (Box 57)
  - Apportionment, 1975-1976 (Box 57)
  - Apportionment, 1977 (Box 57)
  - Bureau of National Affairs, 1975-1978 (codes and regulations) (Box 57)
  - Clipsheet (Legislative Forum) 1976-1978 (Box 57)
  - Conference on Aging, 1981 (Box 57)
  - Congressional Interview, 1980 (Box 57)
  - Constitutional Revision, 1977 (Box 57)
  - Convention, 1979 (Box 57)
  - Convention and By-Laws, 1975 (Box 57)
  - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 57)
  - Education Law, 1975 (Box 57)
  - Education Law, 1976 (Box 57)
  - Education Law, 1977-1978 (Box 57)
  - Education Law, 1979-1980 (Box 57)
  - Election Law, 1977-1978 (Box 57)
  - Election Law, 1979-1980 (Box 58)
  - Energy, 1976-1977 (Box 58)
  - Energy, 1978 (Box 58)
  - Environment Quality, 1975 (Box 58)
  - Environment Quality, 1975-1977 (Box 58)
  - Environment Quality, 1977 (Box 58)
  - Environment Quality-Land Use, 1975 (Box 58)
  - Financing Education, 1972-1976 (Box 58)
  - Financing Education, 1973-1975 (Box 58)
  - Financing Education, 1977 (Box 58)
  - Financing Education, 1978 (Box 58)
  - "Form 99", 1979 (Box 58)
  - Freedom of Information, 1974-1975 (Box 58)
  - General Election, 1975 (Box 58)
  - Good Guys (minutes) 1978 (Box 58)
  - Good Guys (minutes) 1979 (Box 58)
  - Good Guys (minutes) 1981 (Box 58)
  - Government-Rules for Code of Ethics, 1980 (Box 59)
  - Government Operations, 1977 (Box 59)
  - Government Operations, 1978 (Box 59)
  - Government Operations, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Governor, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Governor, 1980 (Box 59)
  - Housing, 1972-1975 (Box 59)
  - Human Resources, 1976-1977 (Box 59)
  - Human Resources, 1977-1978 (Box 59)
  - Human Resources, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Indirect Initiative, 1979 (Box 59)
  - Initiative and Referendum, 1978 (Box 59)
  - Intern, 1977 (Box 59)
  - Judicial, 1974-1975 (Box 59)
  - Judicial, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - Judicial, 1977 (Box 60)
  - Judicial, 1978 (Box 60)
  - Judicial, 1979 (Box 60)
  - Land Use, 1974-1975 (Box 60)
  - Land Use, 1975-1976 (Box 60)
  - Land Use, 1977 (Box 60)
  - League-Miscellaneous, 1978 (Box 60)
  - League-Miscellaneous (National also) 1979 (Box 60)
  - Legislative and Lobbying Procedures-Miscellaneous (Box 61)
  - Legislative Conference, 1975 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Conference, 1976 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Conference, 1977 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Conference, 1978 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Conference, 1979 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Conference, 1980 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Interviews-Albany January 12-13, 1976 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Interviews-Congress (Box 61)
  - Legislative News, 1975 (Box 61)
  - Legislative News, 1976 (Box 61)
  - Legislative News, 1977-1978 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Reform, 1974-1975 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Reform, 1977 (Box 61)
  - Legislative Representatives for Social Concerns, 1975 (Box 61)
  - Legislex, 1979 (Box 61)
  - Legislex, 1981 (Box 61)
  - Lobbying and Action, 1977 (Box 61)
  - Lobbying and Action, 1978 (Box 61)
  - Lobbying and Action, 1979 (Box 61)
  - Lobbying and Action, 1980 (Box 62)
  - Lobbying and Action, 1981 (Box 62)
  - Lobbying Citizen Participation, 1981 (Box 62)
  - Lobbying Committee (Box 62)
  - Lobbying Course, 1979 (Box 62)
  - Lobbying Techniques, 1981 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box 62)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980 (Box 62)
  - National Board Report-Action, 1976 (Box 62)
  - National Baord Reports-Action, 1977-1978 (Box 63)
  - National Item (Urban Crisis, UN Trade) (Box 63)
  - Natural Resources (Box 63)
  - New York State Board Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 63)
  - New York State Board Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 63)
  - New York State Convention, 1977 (Box 63)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1978 (Box 63)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1979 (Box 63)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1980 (Box 63)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1981 (Box 63)
  - Newspaper Clippings-Publicity, 1976 (Box 63)
  - Newspaper Clippings-Publicity, 1977 (Box 63)
  - Press Releases, 1976 (Box 63)
  - Press Releases, 1978 (Box 63)
  - Press Releases, 1979 (Box 63)
  - Press Releases, 1980 (Box 63)
  - Publication and Catalogue Information (Box 63)
  - Reapportionment (Box 64)
  - Report-Legislative Forum (Box 64)
  - Report from the Hill (Box 64)
  - Roll Calls, Voting Records, 1977 (Box 64)
  - Roll Calls, Voting Records, 1978 (Box 64)
  - Roll Calls, Voting Records, 1979 (Box 64)
  - Roll Calls, Voting Records, 1980 (Box 64)
  - Social Services (Box 64)
  - Speaking Engagements (Box 64)
  - State and National League (Box 64)
  - State Board Report (Box 64)
  - State League-Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 64)
  - Testimony, 1977 (Box 64)
  - Testimony, 1978 (Box 64)
  - Testimony, 1979 (Box 64)
  - Testimony, 1980 (Box 64)
  - Testimony, 1981 (Box 64)
  - Transportation, (2 Folders) (Box 64)
  - Transportation in New York State (Box 64)
  - Urban Crisis, 1978 (Box 64)
  - Urban Crisis, 1979, (2 Folders) (Box 64)
  - Vacancies ^helved off-site (Box 65)
  - Voter-New York State (Box 65)
  - Voter Service, 1977 (Focus on Fall ballot) (Box 65)
  - Voter service, 1978 (Box 65)
  - Voter Service, 1979 (Box 65)
  - Voter Service, 1980 (Box 65)
  - Voters (State and National) 1979 (Box 65)
  - Voters (State and National) 1981 (Box 65)
  - Women's Issues (Box 65)
- Series XX: 1990 Addition
  - Subseries XX.1: Subject files (Folders 1-278)
    - Folder no. 1-12 (Box 66)
    - Folder no. 13-27 (Box 67)
    - Folder no. 28-33 (Box 68)
    - Folder no. 34-40 (Box 69)
    - Folder no. 41-46 (Box 70)
    - Folder no. 47-58 (Box 71)
    - Folder no. 59-67 (Box 72)
    - Folder no. 68-70 (Box 73)
    - Folder no. 71-78 (Box 74)
    - Folder no. 79-85 (Box 75)
    - Folder no. 86-94 (Box 76)
    - Folder no. 95-98 (Box 77)
    - Folder no. 99-111 (Box 78)
    - Folder no. 112-122 (Box 79)
    - Folder no. 123-138 (Box 80)
    - Folder no. 139-150 (Box 81)
    - Folder no. 151-161 (Box 82)
    - Folder no. 162-171 (Box 83)
    - Folder no. 172-177 (Box 84)
    - Folder no. 178-186 (Box 85)
    - Folder no. 187-193 (Box 86)
    - Folder no. 194-205 (Box 87)
    - Folder no. 206-215 (Box 88)
    - Folder no. 216-220 (Box 89)
    - Folder no. 221-224 (Box 90)
    - Folder no. 225-240 (Box 91)
    - Folder no. 241-250 (Box 92)
    - Folder no. 251-258 (Box 93)
    - Folder no. 259-265 (Box 94)
    - Folder no. 266-275 (Box 95)
    - Folder no. 276-278 (Box 96)
  - Subseries XX.2:Disbanded League files
    - Folder no. 279-287 (Box 97)
    - Folder no. 288-294 (Box 98)
    - Folder no. 295-314 (Box 99)
    - Folder no. 315-322 (Box 100)
    - Folder no. 323-327 (Box 101)
    - Folder no. 328-329 (Box 102)
    - Folder no. 330-338 (Box 103)
    - Plaques, etc. (Box 104)